{"Name":"영어 문제집 (단어)","Problems":[{"Question":"mom\r\n1.엄마\r\n2.아빠\r\n3.아들","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"엄마\r\n1.dad\r\n2.son\r\n3.mom","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"dad\r\n1.엄마\r\n2.아빠\r\n3.할아버지","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"아빠\r\n1.son\r\n2.dad\r\n3.sister","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"son\r\n1.딸\r\n2.손녀\r\n3.아들","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"아들\r\n1.daughter\r\n2.granddaughter\r\n3.son","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"brother\r\n1.형, 남동생, 오빠\r\n2.언니, 여동생, 누나\r\n3.부모","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"형, 남동생, 오빠\r\n1.brother\r\n2.sister\r\n3.parents","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"sister\r\n1.아기\r\n2.언니, 여동생, 누나\r\n3.아내","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"언니, 여동생, 누나\r\n1.baby\r\n2.sister\r\n3.wife","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"baby\r\n1.아내\r\n2.남편\r\n3.아기","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"아기\r\n1.wife\r\n2.husband\r\n3.baby","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"wife\r\n1.아내\r\n2.남편\r\n3.어머니","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"아내\r\n1.wife\r\n2.husband\r\n3.mother","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"husband\r\n1.아버지\r\n2.남편\r\n3.할아버지","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"남편\r\n1.father\r\n2.husband\r\n3.grandfather","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"daughter\r\n1.아들\r\n2.손자\r\n3.딸","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"딸\r\n1.son\r\n2.grandson\r\n3.daughter","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"parents\r\n1.부모\r\n2.이모\r\n3.고모","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"부모\r\n1.parents\r\n2.aunt\r\n3.uncle","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"father\r\n1.어머니\r\n2.아버지\r\n3.삼촌, 큰아버지","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"아버지\r\n1.mother\r\n2.father\r\n3.uncle","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"mother\r\n1.할머니\r\n2.여동생, 누나, 언니\r\n3.어머니","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"어머니\r\n1.grandmother\r\n2.sister\r\n3.mother","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"uncle\r\n1.삼촌, 큰아버지\r\n2.이모\r\n3.고모","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"삼촌, 큰아버지\r\n1.uncle\r\n2.aunt\r\n3.hunt","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"aunt\r\n1.할아버지\r\n2.이모, 고모\r\n3.할머니","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"이모, 고모\r\n1.grandfather\r\n2.aunt\r\n3.grandmother","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"grandfather\r\n1.아버지\r\n2.손자\r\n3.할아버지","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"할아버지\r\n1.father\r\n2.grandson\r\n3.grandfather","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"grandmother\r\n1.할머니\r\n2.어머니\r\n3.사촌","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"할머니\r\n1.grandmother\r\n2.mother\r\n3.cousin","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"family\r\n1.여자조카\r\n2.가족\r\n3.남자조카","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"가족\r\n1.niece\r\n2.family\r\n3.nephew","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"niece\r\n1.남자조카\r\n2.아버지\r\n3.여자조카","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"여자조카\r\n1.nephew\r\n2.father\r\n3.niece","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"nephew\r\n1.남자조카\r\n2.여자조카\r\n3.어머니","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"남자조카\r\n1.nephew\r\n2.niece\r\n3.mother","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"cousin\r\n1.할아버지\r\n2.사촌\r\n3.여자조카","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"사촌\r\n1.grandfather\r\n2.cousin\r\n3.niece","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"house\r\n1.정원\r\n2.부엌\r\n3.집","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"집\r\n1.garden\r\n2.kitchen\r\n3.house","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"garden\r\n1.정원\r\n2.거실\r\n3.부엌","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"정원\r\n1.garden\r\n2.living room\r\n3.kitchen","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"kitchen\r\n1.욕실\r\n2.부엌\r\n3.거실","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"부엌\r\n1.bathroom\r\n2.kitchen\r\n3.living room","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"living room\r\n1.침실\r\n2.욕실\r\n3.거실","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"거실\r\n1.bedroom\r\n2.bathroom\r\n3.living room","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"bathroom\r\n1.욕실\r\n2.침실\r\n3.마당","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"욕실\r\n1.bathroom\r\n2.bedroom\r\n3.yard","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"bedroom\r\n1.지하실\r\n2.침실\r\n3.마당","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"침실\r\n1.basement\r\n2.bedroom\r\n3.yard","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"yard\r\n1.지하실t\r\n2.다락방\r\n3.마당","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"마당\r\n1.basement\r\n2.attic\r\n3.yard","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"basement\r\n1.지하실\r\n2.차고\r\n3.다락방","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"지하실\r\n1.basement\r\n2.garage\r\n3.attic","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"attic\r\n1.차고\r\n2.다락방\r\n3.벽","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"다락방\r\n1.garage\r\n2.attic\r\n3.wall","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"garage\r\n1.벽\r\n2.창문\r\n3.차고","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"차고\r\n1.wall\r\n2.window\r\n3.garage","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"wall\r\n1.벽\r\n2.문\r\n3.창문","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"벽\r\n1.wall\r\n2.door\r\n3.window","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"window\r\n1.방\r\n2.창문\r\n3.문","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"창문\r\n1.room\r\n2.window\r\n3.door","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"door\r\n1.지붕\r\n2.방\r\n3.문","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"문\r\n1.roof\r\n2.room\r\n3.door","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"room\r\n1.방\r\n2.바닥, 마루\r\n3.지붕","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"방\r\n1.room\r\n2.floor\r\n3.roof","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"roof\r\n1.천장\r\n2.지붕\r\n3.바닥, 마루","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"지붕\r\n1.ceiling\r\n2.roof\r\n3.floor","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"floor\r\n1.굴뚝\r\n2.천장\r\n3.바닥, 마루","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"바닥, 마루\r\n1.chimney\r\n2.ceiling\r\n3.floor","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"ceiling\r\n1.천장\r\n2.굴뚝\r\n3.계단","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"천장\r\n1.ceiling\r\n2.chimney\r\n3.stairs","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"chimney\r\n1.담, 울타리\r\n2.굴뚝\r\n3.계단","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"굴뚝\r\n1.fence\r\n2.chimney\r\n3.stairs","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"2"},{"Question":"stairs\r\n1.담, 울타리\r\n2.집\r\n3.계단","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"계단\r\n1.fence\r\n2.house\r\n3.stairs","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"3"},{"Question":"fence\r\n1.담, 울타리\r\n2.집\r\n3.정원","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"},{"Question":"담, 울타리\r\n1.fence\r\n2.house\r\n3.garden","Choices":[{"Choice":"1"},{"Choice":"2"},{"Choice":"3"}],"Answer":"1"}]}
